// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "It is a judgement of the rightness or wrongness of something or someone, or of the usefulness of something or someone, based on comparison or other relativity.",
    answer: "Value Judgement",
    options: [
      "Value Judgement",
      "Evaluation",
      "Comparison",
      "Venn diagram"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Is a piece of writing that takes a stance on an issue. It persuades the readers to support their claim or point of view.",
    answer: "Argumentative essay",
    options: [
      "Argumentative essay",
      "informative Essay",
      "Narrative Essay",
      "Descriptive Essay"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "It introduces your topic. It informs your audience about the topic of your essay.",
    answer: "Introductory paragraph",
    options: [
      "Introductory paragraph",
      "Body paragraphs",
      "The thesis statement",
      "Conclusion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "It is a one-sentence summary of your main point and claim.",
    answer: "The thesis statement",
    options: [
      "Introductory paragraph",
      "Body paragraphs",
      "The thesis statement",
      "Conclusion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " It comprises three or more paragraph that explains the reason why you support your thesis.",
    answer: "Body paragraphs",
    options: [
      "Introductory paragraph",
      "Body paragraphs",
      "The thesis statement",
      "Conclusion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question:"It restates your thesis and summarize all of the arguments made in your body paragraph.",
    answer: "Conclusion",
    options: [
      "Introductory paragraph",
      "Body paragraphs",
      "The thesis statement",
      "Conclusion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Problem that influences many citizens within a society.",
    answer: "social issue",
    options: [
      "environmental issue",
      "social issue",
      "international issue",
      "national issue"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "It is a method or approach that is proven useful in listening to get information.",
    answer: "TQLR approach",
    options: [
      "Deductive approach",
      "Inductive approach",
      "Abductive approach",
      "TQLR approach"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In TQLR approach, R stands for:",
    answer: "respond",
    options: [
      "Repeat",
      "Restate",
      "respond",
      "recall"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "TQLR stands for:",
    answer: "Evidence",
    options: [
    "Talk, Question, Left, Right",
    "Tune in, Question, Listen, Recall",
    "Tune in, Quarrel, Listen, Respond",
    "Tune in, Question, Listen, Respond"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "is designed to provide an opportunity for a group to hear several people knowledgeable about specific topic.",
    answer: "Panel discussion",
    options: [
      "Panel discussion",
      "Primary groups",
      "secondary Groups ",
      "Open Forum"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Use to provide factual information regarding current problems, determine social values",
    answer: "Public Panel Discussion",
    options: [
      "Educational Panel Discussion",
      "Critical Discussion",
      "Public Panel Discussion",
      "Hypothetical Discussion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Use in educational institutions to provide factual and conceptual knowledge and clarification of certain theories and principles",
    answer: "Educational Panel Discussion",
    options: [
      "Educational Panel Discussion",
      "Critical Discussion",
      "Public Panel Discussion",
      "Hypothetical Discussion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "He/she plans how, where and when panel discussion will be organized.",
    answer: "Instructor",
    options: [
      "Panelist",
      "Audience",
      "Moderator",
      "Instructor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Keeps the discussion on the theme and encourages interaction among members. summarizes & highlights the points.",
    answer: "Moderator",
    options: [
      "Panelist",
      "Audience",
      "Moderator",
      "Instructor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Members who sit in a semi-circle shape in front of the audience and must have the mastery of the subject.",
    answer: "Panelist",
    options: [
      "Panelist",
      "Audience",
      "Moderator",
      "Instructor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 17,
    question: "allowed to put question and seek clarification.",
    answer: "Audience",
    options: [
      "Panelist",
      "Audience",
      "Moderator",
      "Instructor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 18,
    question: "The following are the Advantages of a panel discussion Except?",
    answer: "It requires more time of planning, organizing and presentation.",
    options: [
      "It facilitates clarification on knotty issues.",
      "It requires more time of planning, organizing and presentation.",
      "It highlights the multi-dimensionality of the issue under discussion.",
      "It helps to develop critical thinking in both panelists and the audience"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 19,
    question: "The following are the principal responsibilities of an instructor in a panel discussion EXCEPT:",
    answer: "Close the discussion and provides a summary of panel presentations and discussion.",
    options: [
      "Identify or help participants identify, issues or topics.",
      "Ensure that all panelists and the moderator are familiar with the procedures for panel discussion.",
      "Assist panelists and participants (when necessary) in preparation for the discussion.",
      "Close the discussion and provides a summary of panel presentations and discussion."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 20,
    question: "The following procedures have been used effectively EXCEPT:",
    answer: "The leader or moderator teaches students to think of the issues under consideration and ask relevant questions.",
    options: [
      "The leader or moderator introduces the topic and the panelists present their views and opinions regarding the issue or topic for a set amount of time.",
      "The panelists discuss the issue or topic with each other by asking questions or reacting to the views and opinions of other panel members.",
      "The leader or moderator closes the discussion and provides a summary of panel presentations and discussion.",
      "The leader or moderator teaches students to think of the issues under consideration and ask relevant questions."
    ]
  },
  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];